Guide to the Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, J. Dennis O'Connor, Administrative Files, 1991-1995 UA.2.10.1991-1995
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Mail Log Files, 1991-1995; I.
  - Department of Athletics, 5.
    - Golden Panthers, 5.10.
      - 5.10. Golden Panthers, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - 5.10. Golden Panthers, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 26)
      - 5.10. Golden Panthers, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Sports Information, 5.11.
      - 5.11. Sports Information, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - 5.11. Sports Information, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - 5.11. Sports Information, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Athletics Complaints [RESTRICTED], 5.12.
      - 5.12. Athletics Complaints [RESTRICTED], 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - 5.12. Athletics Complaints [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Clerk of the Senate, 6.
    The files in the 6.0 Mail Log concern the University of Pittsburgh's Senate and Faculty Assembly. There are meeting minutes and information on the overall organizations, as well as the Senate's individual committees. Some correspondence and reports are also available.
    - Clerk of the Senate, 6.0.
      - 6.0. Clerk of the Senate, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - 6.0. Clerk of the Senate, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - 6.0. Clerk of the Senate, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - University Senate, 6.1.
      - 206.03. University Senate, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - 6.1. University Senate, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - 6.1. University Senate, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - 6.1. University Senate, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 39-40)
    - Educational Policies Committee, 6.1.1.
      - 6.1.1. Educational Policies Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - 6.1.1. Educational Policies Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Budget Policies Committee, 6.1.2.
      - 6.1.2. Budget Policies Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - 6.1.2. Budget Policies Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Tenure and Academic Freedom Committee, 6.1.3.
      - 6.1.3. Tenure and Academic Freedom Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Athletics Committee, 6.1.4.
      - 6.1.4. Athletics Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - 6.1.4. Athletics Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Senate Affairs Committee, 6.1.5.
      - 6.1.5. Senate Affairs Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Senate Council, 6.2.
      - 6.2. Senate Council, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - 6.2. Senate Council, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - 6.2. Senate Council, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - 6.2. Senate Council, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Chancellor's Remarks to Senate Council, 6.2.1.
      - 6.2.1. Chancellor's Remarks to Senate Council, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Faculty Assembly, 6.3.
      - 206.05. Faculty Assembly, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 54)
      - 6.3. Faculty Assembly, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - 6.3. Faculty Assembly, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - 6.3. Faculty Assembly, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Affirmative Action, 7.
    The files in the 7.0 Mail Log contain reports, policies and statements relating to affirmative action at the university. Topics include complaints and evaluations of discrimination, racism and harassment, as well as Title IX violations. Affirmative Action data reports, which contain information about hiring and enrollment demographics, are also present.
    - Affirmative Action, 7.0.
      - 202.00. Affirmative Action, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 58-59)
      - 7.0. Affirmative Action, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
      - 7.0. Affirmative Action, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
      - 7.0. Affirmative Action, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 7-8)
  - Office of the Provost, 8.
    The 8.0 Mail Log files contain material on everything that falls under the purview of the Office of the Provost. This includes material on individual schools and centers that report to the Provost, the Boards of Visitors for these schools, the University Library System, the Nationality Rooms Program, the Semester at Sea program, the Institute of Politics, and material on the four branch campuses of the University of Pittsburgh. The records include correspondence between administrators as well as faculty members, departmental information, reports, some publications, meeting information, and future plans for the different reporting groups.
    - Office of the Provost, 8.0.
      - 800.00. Office of the Provost, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - 8.0. Office of the Provost, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
      - 8.0. Office of the Provost, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 12-14)
      - 8.0. Office of the Provost, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 1-3)
      - 8.0. Office of the Provost, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 4-7)
      - 8.0. Office of the Provost, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Professors Emeritus, 8.0.2.
      - 800.04. Professors Emeritus, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - 8.0.2. Professors Emeritus, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - 8.0.2. Professors Emeritus, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Distinguished Service Professorships, 8.0.3.
      - 8.0.3. Distinguished Service Professorships, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - 8.0.3. Distinguished Service Professorships, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Promotion and Tenure, 8.0.5.
      - 8.0.5. Promotion and Tenure, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - 8.0.5. Promotion and Tenure, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Retirements, 8.0.6.
      - 8.0.6. Retirements, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - 8.0.6. Retirements, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - 8.0.6. Retirements, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Provost's Advisory Committee on Women's Concerns (PACWC), 8.0.7.
      - 8.0.7. Provost's Advisory Committee on Women's Concerns (PACWC), 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - 8.0.7. Provost's Advisory Committee on Women's Concerns (PACWC), 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Associate Provost for Graduate Studies, 8.0.8.
      - 8.0.8. Associate Provost for Graduate Studies [RESTRICTED], 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - 8.0.8. Associate Provost for Graduate Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Academic Calendar, 8.0.8.1.
      - 8.0.8.1. Academic Calendar, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 23)
      - 8.0.9. Academic Calendar, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, 8.0.10.
      - 805.00. Associate Provost for Undergraduate Education, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 25)
      - 8.0.10. Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - 8.0.11. Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Associate Provost for Research, 8.0.11.
      - 8.0.11. Associate Provost for Research, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 28)
      - 8.0.11. Associate Provost for Research, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - 8.0.11. Associate Provost for Research, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - 8.0.12. Associate Provost for Research, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
    - Research Integrity Officer, 8.0.11.1.
      - 803.00A. Research Integrity Officer, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - 8.0.11.1. Research Integrity Officer, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - 8.0.11.1. Research Integrity Officer, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
      - 8.0.13. Research Integrity Officer, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - University Research Council, 803.01C.
      - 803.01C. University Research Council, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Patent Committee, 803.01B.
      - 803.01B. Patent Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Council of Deans, 8.0.12.
      - 8.0.12. Council of Deans, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - 8.0.12. Council of Deans, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - 8.0.14. Council of Deans, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 8.0.13.
      - 800.06. Planning and Resource Management (PRMS), 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
      - 8.0.13. Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 16-17)
      - 8.0.13. Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 18-19)
      - 8.0.15. Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - 8.0.15. Planning and Resource Management System (PRMS), 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 8.1.
      - 802.00. Dean, Faculty of Arts & Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
      - 8.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
      - 8.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 8-12)
      - 8.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - 8.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
      - 8.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences (FAS), 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Faculty of Arts & Sciences Board of Visitors, 8.1.1.
      - 8.1.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - 8.1.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - 8.1.1. Faculty of Arts & Sciences Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - FAS Gazette, 8.1.2.
      - 802.02. FAS Gazette, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - 8.1.2. FAS Gazette, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - 8.1.2. FAS Gazette, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - 8.1.2. FAS Gazette, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Superconducting Supercollider, 802.03.
      - 802.03. Superconducting Supercollider, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Graduate Studies, 8.1.4.
      - 802.11. Graduate Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - 8.1.4. Graduate Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - 8.1.4. Graduate Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - 8.1.4. Graduate Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - 8.1.4. Graduate Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Jazz Seminar, 8.1.5.
      - 8.1.5. Jazz Seminar, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - College of Arts & Sciences (CAS), 8.2.
      - 802.12. College of Arts & Sciences, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - 8.2. College of Arts & Sciences, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 20)
      - 8.2. College of Arts & Sciences, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
      - 8.2. College of Arts & Sciences, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - CAS Board of Visitors, 8.2.1.
      - 8.2.1. CAS Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 8.3.
      - 801.01. Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 24)
      - 8.3. Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
      - 8.3. Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 27-29)
      - 8.3. Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - 8.3. Katz Graduate School of Business (KGSB), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - KGSB Board of Visitors, 8.3.1.
      - 801.01A. KGSB Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - 8.3.1. KGSB Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - 8.3.1. KGSB Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - 8.3.1. KGSB Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - 8.3.1. KGSB Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Czechoslovak Management Center, 8.3.3.
      - 801.01C. Czechoslovak Management Center, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - 8.3.3. Czechoslovak Management Center, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - 8.3.3. Czechoslovak Management Center, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - 8.3.3. Czechoslovak Management Center, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Center for Economic Research and Graduate Education (CERGE), 8.3.4.
      - 8.3.4. Center for Economic Research and Graduate Education (CERGE), 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - 8.3.4. Center for Economic Research and Graduate Education (CERGE), 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - 8.3.4. Center for Economic Research and Graduate Education (CERGE), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - College of Business Administration, 8.3.5.
      - 8.3.5. College of Business Administration, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - College of General Studies (CGS), 8.4.
      - 801.06. College of General Studies (CGS), 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - 8.4. College of General Studies (CGS), 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - 8.4. College of General Studies (CGS), 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - 8.4. College of General Studies (CGS), 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - CGS Board of Visitors, 8.4.1.
      - 801.06B. CGS Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - 8.4.1. CGS Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - 8.4.1. CGS Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
      - 8.4.1. CGS Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - School of Education, 8.5.
      - 801.02. School of Education, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - 8.5. School of Education, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - 8.5. School of Education, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 26-27)
      - 8.5. School of Education, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - School of Engineering, 8.6.
      - 801.03. School of Engineering, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - 8.6. School of Engineering, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 30)
      - 8.6. School of Engineering, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 31-32)
      - 8.6. School of Engineering, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - 8.6. School of Engineering, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 8.6.1.
      - 801.03B. School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - 8.6.1. School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - 8.6.1. School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
      - 8.6.1. School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - 8.6.1. School of Engineering Board of Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Pittsburgh Coal Conference, 8.6.3.
      - 8.6.3. Pittsburgh Coal Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - 8.6.3. Pittsburgh Coal Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - School of Law, 8.7.
      - 801.04. School of Law, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - 8.7. School of Law, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - 8.7. School of Law, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 13-14)
      - 8.7. School of Law, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 15-16)
    - School of Law Board of Visitors, 8.7.1.
      - 801.04A. School of Law Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - 8.7.1. School of Law Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - 8.7.1. School of Law Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - 8.7.1. School of Law Board of Visitors, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - School of Library and Information Science (SLIS), 8.8.
      - 801.09. School of Library and Information Science (SLIS), 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - 8.8. School of Library and Information Science (SLIS), 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 22)
      - 8.8. School of Library and Information Science (SLIS), 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 23)
      - 8.8. School of Library and Information Science (SLIS), 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - SLIS Board of Visitors, 8.8.1.
      - 801.09A. SLIS Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 25)
      - 8.8.1. SLIS Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - 8.8.1. SLIS Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - 8.8.1. SLIS Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), 8.9.
      - 801.11. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), 1991-1992 (Box 29, Folder 29)
      - 8.9. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - 8.9. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - 8.9. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs (GSPIA), 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 32-33)
    - GSPIA Board of Visitors, 8.9.1.
      - 8.9.1. GSPIA Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - 8.9.1. GSPIA Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - 8.9.1. GSPIA Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Matthew B. Ridgway Center for International Security Studies, 8.9.2.
      - 801.11B. Matthew B. Ridgway Center for International Security Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - 8.9.2. Matthew B. Ridgway Center for International Security Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - 8.9.2. Matthew B. Ridgway Center for International Security Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - International Management Development Institute (IMDI), 8.9.3.
      - 8.9.3. International Management Development Institute (IMDI), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - 8.9.3. International Management Development Institute (IMDI), 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - 8.9.3. International Management Development Institute (IMDI), 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - School of Social Work, 8.10.
      - 801.05. School of Social Work, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
      - 8.10. School of Social Work, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - 8.10. School of Social Work, 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 14-15)
      - 8.10. School of Social Work, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 16-17)
    - School of Social Work Board of Visitors, 8.10.1.
      - 801.05A. School of Social Work Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - 8.10.1. School of Social Work Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - University Center for International Studies (UCIS), 8.11.
      - 801.07. University Center for International Studies (UCIS), 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - 8.11. University Center for International Studies (UCIS), 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - 8.11. University Center for International Studies (UCIS), 1993-1994 (Box 30, Folder 22-23)
      - 8.11. University Center for International Studies (UCIS), 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 24-25)
    - UCIS Board of Visitors, 8.11.1.
      - 801.05A. UCIS Board of Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - 8.11.1. UCIS Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - 8.11.1. UCIS Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - 8.11.1. UCIS Board of Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Latin American Studies, 8.11.2.
      - 801.07B. Latin American Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - 8.11.2. Latin American Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - 8.11.2. Latin American Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - 8.11.2. Latin American Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Governor's School of International Studies, 8.11.3.
      - 801.07C. Governor's School of International Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - 8.11.3. Governor's School of International Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - 8.11.3. Governor's School of International Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - 8.11.3. Governor's School of International Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - International Delegations and Visitors, 8.11.4.
      - 801.07D. International Delegations and Visitors, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - 8.11.4. International Delegations and Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - 8.11.4. International Delegations and Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - 8.11.4. International Delegations and Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Semester at Sea, 8.11.5.
      - 801.07E. Semester at Sea, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - 8.11.5. Semester at Sea, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - 8.11.5. Semester at Sea, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - 8.11.5. Semester at Sea, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 19-20)
    - Institute of European Studies, 8.11.6.
      - 8.11.6. Institute of European Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - 8.11.6. Institute of European Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - 8.11.6. Institute of European Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Russian and European Studies, 8.11.7.
      - 801.07G. Russian and European Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - 8.11.7. Russian and European Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - 8.11.7. Russian and European Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 26)
      - 8.11.7. Russian and European Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Heinz Fellowship Program, 8.11.8.
      - 8.11.8. Heinz Fellowship Program, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Asian Studies Program and Institute of Chinese Studies, 8.11.9.
      - 801.07J. Asian Studies Program and Institute of Chinese Studies, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 29)
      - 8.11.9. Asian Studies Program and Institute of Chinese Studies, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 30)
      - 8.11.9. Asian Studies Program and Institute of Chinese Studies, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 31)
      - 8.11.9. Asian Studies Program and Institute of Chinese Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - International University Cooperative Agreements, 8.11.10.
      - 801.07M. International University Cooperative Agreements, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 33)
      - 8.11.10. International University Cooperative Agreements, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 34)
      - 8.11.10. International University Cooperative Agreements, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 35)
      - 8.11.10. International University Cooperative Agreements, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Pittsburgh Council for International Visitors, 8.11.11.
      - 8.11.11. Pittsburgh Council for International Visitors, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Wuhan University and Pittsburgh-Wuhan Friendship Committee, 8.11.13.
      - 8.11.13. Wuhan University and Pittsburgh-Wuhan Friendship Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 38)
      - 8.11.13.Wuhan University and Pittsburgh-Wuhan Friendship Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Europe Business Opportunity Conference, 8.11.14.
      - 8.11.14. Europe Business Opportunity Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 40-41)
    - Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC), 8.12.
      - 801.08. Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC), 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
      - 8.12. Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC), 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - 8.12. Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC), 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - 8.12. Learning Research and Development Center (LRDC), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - LRDC Board of Visitors, 8.12.1.
      - 8.12.1. LRDC Board of Visitors, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - 8.12.1. LRDC Board of Visitors, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - University Center for Social & Urban Research (UCSUR), 8.13.
      - 801.12. University Center for Social & Urban Research (UCSUR), 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - 8.13. University Center for Social & Urban Research (UCSUR), 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 9-10)
      - 8.13. University Center for Social & Urban Research (UCSUR), 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 11-13)
      - 8.13. University Center for Social & Urban Research (UCSUR), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 14-15)
    - University Honors College (UHC), 8.14.
      - 8.14. University Honors College (UHC), 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - 8.14. University Honors College (UHC), 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - 8.14. University Honors College (UHC), 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Chancellor's Scholars, 8.14.2.
      - 801.14B. Chancellor's Scholars, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - 8.14.2. Chancellor's Scholars, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - 8.14.2. Chancellor's Scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - 8.14.2. Chancellor's Scholars, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Truman Scholars, 8.14.3.
      - 8.14.3. Truman Scholars, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 8.14.4.
      - 801.14D. Chancellor's Evening Scholars, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 24)